http://www.gymjones.com/privacy

JOIN THE GYM JONESMAILING LIST.
Content
Do not fill in this field. It is an anti-spam measure.
SUBSCRIBE
No thanks, maybe later.
PRIVACY POLICY
This policy (the “Privacy Policy”) covers how Gym Jones, LLC (the “Company”) treats personal information that the Company collects and receives through your use of the website GymJones.com. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any websites and/or company that you may be directed to via GymJones.com that the Company does not directly own or control, or to people that the Company does not employ or manage, including any website and/or social media website operated by any fully certified instructors and/or "Disciples" identified on GymJones.com. By using this website, you indicate your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, then do not access, view or otherwise use GymJones.com.
Collecting Information
The Company collects personal information from you, including but not limited to financial information, when you access GymJones.com, register with GymJones.com and/or subscribe to subscription-based content provided by GymJones.com. The Company does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies and/or individuals without your express written permission, unless required by the laws of the State of Utah or pursuant to federal law. All information collected about you in the process of your registering with GymJones.com or subscribing to GymJones.com's subscription-based content shall be kept private and confidential and only employees and/or agents of the Company who reasonably need access to your personal information shall have access to your personal information. All credit card information entered into GymJones.com shall be transmitted to www.stripe.com for processing and will not be stored by Gym Jones, LLC.
Accordingly, Gym Jones, LLC is not responsible for the use, misuse and/or storage of your credit card information and any credit card information entered into GymJones.com shall be governed by terms of use and privacy policies used by www.stripe.com.
Cookies
The Company may set and access GymJones.com "cookies" on your computer upon your accessing GymJones.com.
The Company may let other companies set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not the policies set forth by GymJones.com
Policy Updates
The Company may update this Privacy Policy without notice and at any time in its sole discretion.
Contact
Gym Jones, LLC - salvation@gymjones.com
Effective Date
This privacy policy is effective as of Feb 11th, 2015.
WHO ARE WE?
Hey Friend!
It looks like your credit card information has expired. Let's get that taken care of!
UPDATE INFO
Change Password
SUBMIT
MAKE PLAN ACTIVE?
Current plan will no longer be active.
YES
CANCEL
YOU'VE COMPLETED
MAN OF STEEL
View saved training plans or browse all training plans that are available.
MY TRAINING
TRAINING PLANS
